(Howard(to Raj who has whispered to him):)Do you really think your lips in my ear
is helping?
(Penny(arriving):)-Hi. Sorry I'm late.
-Oh, glad you're here.
(Leonard:)Sit down, I'll get you a plate.
Mom, you remember Penny?
Oh, yes, the waitress/actress
with the unresolved father issues.
(Beverley:)Has he finally come to terms
with his little slugger growing breasts?
(Penny:)Well, he sent me a football
and a catcher's mitt for Christmas...
...so I'm gonna say no.
(Howard:)If it helps,
we're all good with your breasts.
(Beverley:)Classic overcompensation.
(Beverley:)Oh, speaking of fathers, Leonard,
that reminds me. I'm divorcing yours.
(Penny:)-What?
-Yes. He was cheating on me.
(Sheldon:)-No.
BEVERLY: Yes.
(Beverley:)With some waitress
from the university cafeteria.
(Beverley:)Can you believe it? A waitress.
(Beverley:)Oh, no offense, dear.
(Penny:)No, it sounded like a compliment.
(Leonard:)-When did this happen?
-Well, let's see.
(Beverley:)Sheldon, when did I
leave Leonard's father?